老天爷啊
Oh, boy.
干嘛
What?
我无法在不违法协议的情况下 批评你的作品
I can't comment without violating our agreement that i'll not criticize your work.
那你还说"老天爷"
Then what was "Oh, boy"?
我已经相当克制自己了
Great restraint on my part.
我的科学研究没有问题
There's nothing wrong with the science here.
你所谓的"科学研究"  跟我的相比
Perhaps you mean a different thing than I do
相差甚远吧
when you say, "Science."
这样呢
Okay, how's that?
其实刚刚的才是对的
You actually had it right in the first place.
你又掉进我的 经典恶作剧陷阱了
Once again, you've fallen for one of my classic pranks.
气死你
Bazinga!
收到一封很怪的邮件
Now here's a peculiar e-mail.
大学校长要我明天早上8点
The president of the university wants me to meet him
去他办公室见他
at his office tomorrow morning at 8:00 a.m.
-为什么  -没说
- Why? - It doesn't say.
肯定是紧急事件
It must be an emergency.
大学里的人都知道  我8点吃早餐
Everyone at the university knows I eat breakfast at 8:00
8点20肠胃开始消化
and move my bowels at 8:20.
没用啁啾鸟网站前过的是什么日子
Yes, how did we live before Twitter?
明天早上就知道什么事了
I guess you'll find out what it is in the morning.
还要14个小时呢
That's 14 hours away.
接下来840分钟
For the next 840 minutes,
我会像海森堡的粒子
I'm effectively one of Heisenberg's particles;
只知道自己的地点或移动速度
I know where I am or I know how fast I'm going,
但却不能同时知道两者
but I can't know both.
那我怎么受得了
Yet how am I supposed to carry on
这些恼人的东西老在我脑子里乱转
with this huge annoying thing hovering over my head?
我很清楚这种感觉
Yeah, I know the feeling.
《生活大爆炸》
第二季  第23集（本季终）
莱纳德
Leonard? Leonard?
Leonard?
谢尔顿  现在是早上2点啊
Sheldon, it's 2:00 in the morning.
怎么每个人都跟我说现在几点
Why is everybody keep telling me what time it is?
每个人
Everybody?
你  大学校长 还有他妻子
You, the president of the university, his wife,
他们气急败坏的女儿
their sullen teenage daughter.
他们全家都对现在几点 别人知不知道很感兴趣
That entire family is fascinated by what time it is and whether people know it.
你居然在半夜跑去 塞伯特校长家
You went to President Seibert's house in the middle of the night?
他没回复我的邮件
He didn't respond to my e-mail,
我又不知道他的电话
his phone number is unlisted.
那我还能怎么办
Tell me what my other option was.
你可以等到早上啊
You could have waited until morning.
对  对于你是不可能
I know, look who I'm talking to.
你还记得我向
Do you remember the grant proposal I submitted
国家科学基金会提交的 申请去北极勘测
to the National Science Foundation to detect slow-moving monopoles
慢速磁单极子的申请吗
at the magnetic North Pole?
一天不记都不行呢
Hardly a day goes by when I don't think about it.
你真好
Aw, how nice.
基金会的北极考察队员
Well, a space opened up
确定最后一刻  空出了空位
at the last minute on the NSF expedition to the Arctic Circle.
等等
Wait a minute.
他批准让你去北极
He offered to send you to the North Pole?
对
Yes.
他还相当热情呢
In fact, he was quite enthusiastic.
他说"坦白说"
He said, "Frankly,
"我巴不得今晚就送你去"
if I could send you tonight, I would."
那你想去吗
Okay, well, do you want to go?
当然不想
Of course not.
我是理论物理学家
I'm a theoretical physicist.
我选这个职业完全出于能在家办公
A career I chose in no small part because it's indoors,
但如果我能在北极 勘测出慢速磁单极子
but if I'm able to detect slow-moving magnetic monopoles there,
我就能成为证明弦理论的科学家
I will be the scientis to confirm string theory.
人们会写书赞扬我
People will write books about me.
三年级学生会做意粉画 描绘我的一生呢
Third-graders will create macaroni-art dioramas depicting scenes from my life.
当然  说不定画个我揍死你的场景
Sure, maybe a tableau of me trying to pummel you to death.
冷嘲热讽?
Sarcasm?
有可能
Maybe.
真叫人难以取舍
I'm on the horns of a dilemma.
你能想象我  谢尔顿·库珀  在北极吗
Can you imagine me, Sheldon Cooper, at the North Pole?
小菜一碟  我现在就想着呢
Easy peasy, I'm doing it right now.
但我怕冷啊  莱纳德
I'm not good with cold, Leonard.
我们都多少次因为我喝冰吸太快
How often have we had to leave a movie theater
结果头疼
because I got a headache
提前离开电影院了
from drinking the Icee too fast?
我不能去
I can't go.
那就别去
Well, then don't go.
你怎么能这么说
How can you say that?
难得的科学机遇就在眼前
The scientific opportunity of a lifetime
我最好的朋友却让我不要去
presents itself and my best friend says "Don't go."
那就去呗
All right, then go.
听听你说的话
Listen to you.
我怎么去啊
How can I possibly go?
谢尔顿  我到底要说什么
Sheldon, what are the words I can say right now
才能结束这个话题  让我回去睡觉
to end this conversation and let me go back to sleep?
真奇怪  塞伯特校长也这么问我
Odd, President Seibert posed the exact same question.
结果呢
How was it resolved?
没结果  她妻子放狗咬我 结果没下文了
It wasn't. His wife set their dogs on me and rendered the question moot.
想象一下  如果他答应了
Just imagine. If he says yes,
我们就能享受整个没谢尔顿的夏天
we'll have an entire summer without Sheldon.
我们能去户外玩儿
We could play outside.
我们能坐在沙发左边
We could sit on the left side of the couch.
我能在8点20上厕所
I could use the bathroom at 8:20.
我们的梦想真渺小啊
Our dreams are very small, aren't they?
好消息  先生们  我暂时接受了
Good news, gentlemen, I have tentatively accepted...
好耶
Yeah!
加入北极考察队的邀请
...the invitation to join the Arctic Expedition.
-没有你怎么行  -祝马到成功
- It's not gonna be the same without you. - Godspeed.
谢谢 但别高兴得太早
Thank you, but your sentiments may be premature.
我有不祥的预感
Ooh, I don't like where this is going.
我正式提议
I would like to propose...
你们三个和我一起去
that the three of you accompany me.
去北极?
To the North Pole?
是滴
Yes.
是为了确保你走后 我们不会碰你的东西么
Is this just so we won't touch your stuff while you're away?
我承认我是有此顾虑
I'll admit that was a concern.
但事实是
But the fact is,
我需要一个团队协助我
I'll need a support team.
你们三个呢
And the three of you
是我的最佳人选
are my first choice.
真的
Really?
的确有很多人比你们更加够格
Well, there are others who might be more qualified,
但一想到要面试他们我就胃疼
but the thought of interviewing them gave me a stomachache.
我知道这个提议比较重大
Now, I know I'm proposing an enormous undertaking,
你们花几分钟讨论一下吧
so why don't you take a few moments to discuss it?
我们不会真要和他
We're not really gonna go to the North Pole
跑去北极吧
with him, are we?
我现在还能听得到
I'm still within earshot!
你们得等我把门关上
You may want to wait for my door to close.
我们不会真要和他
We're not really gonna go
跑去北极吧
to the North Pole with him, are we?
等下  咱们想想
Hang on. Let's talk about it.
这是国家科学基金探险项目
This is a National Science Foundation expedition.
咱们怎么能拒绝呢
I don't know how we can turn it down.
简单  不是说我们不想参加基金探险项目
Easy. Instead of saying, "No, we don't want to go on an NSF expedition,"
而是我们不想花
say, "No, we don't want to spend
跟一个疯子杵在北极圈的小木屋里
"three months stuck in a cabin in the Arctic Circle
长达三个月
with an anal nutbag."
但如果我们能成为证实弦理论团队的一员
But if we were part of the team that confirmed string theory,
我们就能去任何大学城的酒吧免费喝酒
we could drink for free in any bar in any college town
只要那个大学有比较强的科学研究组织
with a university that has a strong science program.
霍华德  这可是重大科研项目
Howard, this is big science.
你可以成为那个组建仪器的工程师
You could be the engineer who builds the equipment
我们能因此上杂志封面呢
that puts us on the cover of magazines.
我也可以成为那个造出一把弩弓
I could also be the engineer
用来射杀谢尔顿的工程师
who builds the crossbow that kills Sheldon.
你仍然可能因此上杂志
You still might get on a magazine.
你们俩真的慎重考虑过了
So you guys are seriously considering this?
-是的  -你们觉得能受得了谢尔顿
- Yes. - And you think you can put up with Sheldon?
我是印度人嘛
Well, I'm a Hindu.
我的信仰告诉我  今生的苦难
My religion teaches that if we suffer in this life
来世将转为福音
we are rewarded in the next.
和谢尔顿在北极历练三个月
Three months at the North Pole with Sheldon,
我能重生成一个身材火爆又会飞的亿万富翁
and I'm reborn as a well-hung billionaire with wings!
先生们  做出决定了么
Well, gentlemen, have you reached a decision?
我加入
I'm in.
我也加入
Me, too.
晕死  给我压力  从了
Oh, damn it. Peer pressure. Fine.
很好
Excellent.
友情提示下
Just an FYI,
既然我是考察队的队长
as I am the expedition's team leader,
按规定你应该说"好的  队长"
protocol dictates that be phrased, "Fine, sir."
不过别担心
But don't worry,
会有新生培训的
there will be a briefing.
佩妮
Penny.
谢尔顿
Sheldon.
佩妮
Penny.
谢尔顿
Sheldon.
佩妮
Penny.
谢尔顿
Sheldon.
佩妮
Penny.
谢尔顿
Sheldon.
佩妮
Penny!
谢尔顿
Sheldon!
佩妮
Penny!
你要干嘛
What do you want?
我想进入芝士蛋糕厂的步入式冷藏室
I need access to the Cheesecake Factory's walk-in freezer.
亲爱的  我说过了
Now, honey, I already told you, the hamburger
汉堡的肉饼是冷鲜保存的
meat is fresh and stored at a safe temperature.
不  这回是为了三个月的北极考察训练
No. This is to train for a three-month expedition to the magnetic North Pole.
什么
What?
我不知道这句话 哪里让你听不懂了
I don't know how that sentence could possibly confuse you...
说详细点  我将和莱纳德  沃罗威茨  库萨帕里
but to elaborate, I'm going to the Arctic Circle
一切去北极圈
with Leonard, Wolowitz and Koothrappali.
你们都去
You're all going?
-是的  -去三个月
- Yes. - For three months?
是的
Yes.
不好意思
Excuse me.
冷藏室的事你到底是同意还是不同意啊
Is that a yes or a no on the freezer?
这女人的注意力跟小虫虫差不多
The woman has the attention span of a gnat.
-嗨  莱纳德  -嗨
- Hey, Leonard. - Hey.
谢尔顿说你们要去北极
Sheldon says you're going to the North Pole.
是啊  另类吧
Yeah. Pretty cool, huh?
是啊  只是有点惊讶  你没告诉我
Yeah. I'm just a little surprised you didn't tell me.
事情发生得太快了
Oh, well, it all happened kind of fast.
我们忙着体检  买保暖内衣
And we had to get physicals and buy thermal underwear
还得研究下  积雪这些东西
and study up on, you know, snow and stuff.
抱歉  我本来要告诉你的
Sorry, I was gonna tell you.
你不用道歉
Oh, hey, no, you don't have to apologize.
没有说你必须告诉我
There's no reason you have to tell me.
我只不过  有点惊讶罢了
I was just... you know, surprised.
是啊  你很忙
Yes, yes, you were busy,
你很惊讶  激动人心
you were surprised, all very fascinating.
冷藏室的事说到哪了
Now where do we stand on the freezer?
他说真的吗
Is he serious?
事实上  会有帮助的
Actually, it would help.
好吧  我尽量吧
All right, I'll see what I can do.
去北极呆三个月
So, three months at the North Pole.
真是
Wow, that is...
棒极了
awesome.
是啊
Yeah.
不好意思  你所谓的"尽量"
I'm sorry, but at what point do you put this
到底是什么意思
"see what you can do" plan into action?
给你提个醒  谢尔顿
Just a warning, Sheldon.
那个冷藏室是从外面锁门的
The freezer locks from the outside.
-你觉得她难过吗  -没有
- She seems upset to you? - No.
- Did she seem upset to you? - No.
很好  我猜对了
Oh, good, I got it right.
你难过吗
Are you upset?
有一点
A little bit.
两击两中  我真厉害
Two for two. I'm on fire.
我知道她不是我的女朋友
I mean, I know she's not my girlfriend or anything,
但是你不觉得我整个夏天都不在
but wouldn't you think she'd feel a little bad
她会感到些许的难过吗
that I'm going to be gone for the whole summer?
感觉像个附加题
That feels like a bonus question.
见好就收啦  我好开心哦
I'm gonna stop here while I'm ahead but I've had a great time.
好了  这次的训练目的
All right, the purpose of this drill
是使我们适应在即将面对的 北极圈内极度寒冷的温度下
is to acclimate us to the use of tools in extreme temperatures
使用各种工具
such as we will face in the Arctic Circle.
你的工具呢
Where are your tools?
就在这里
Right here.
好了  队员们  打开练习工具箱
All right, team, open up your practice kits.
由于校方不允许我
As the university did not permit me
把实际用到的器材带到
to bring the actual equipment we'll be using
蛋糕厂来  因为貌似呢
to the Cheesecake Factory, because apparently,
我简直"不可理喻"
I'm "ridiculous,"
我提供的替代器材
I've provided substitutes
将极好地锻炼你们的动手技巧
which will exercise your fine motor skills.
莱纳德  你要处理一系列 复杂的数学问题
Leonard, you will be doing a series of complex mathematical problems
使用我在3年级时勇夺 地球科学金牌时获得的
on a vintage Casio model 1175 calculator watch I received
老式卡西欧1175型计算器手表
when I won the Earth Science medal in 3rd grade.
要好好待它
Treat it with respect.
拉杰  你要在 六英寸高的精灵王子模型上
Raj, you will be painting sideburns and a Van Dyke
画出连鬓胡和短尖髯
on a six-inch figurine of Legolas the elf.
记住了
Now, remember,
短尖髯是没有八字胡的山羊胡
a Van Dyke is a goatee without a mustache.
沃罗威茨  你要在
Wolowitz, you will be completing
经典儿童游戏"手术"上面
a series of delicate surgical procedures
完成一系列精细外科手术
on the classic children's game "Operation."
首先
To begin with, you will
切除尺骨  赢得200美刀
"remove funny bone for two hundred dollars."
我去麻省理工就因为这个
For this I went to MIT.
开始
And begin.
我好像吞了一些颜料
I think I swallowed some paint!
带着手套  我按不了按键
I can't press any of the buttons with my gloves.
冻死我了
Oh, son of a bitch!
万事开头难
Adversity is to be expected.
继续
Continue.
靠  这下我要被起诉了
Oh, boy, am I gonna get sued.
我做不到
Okay, I can't do this.
我也做不到
Me either.
先生们  想象一下
Gentlemen, use your imagination.
创新
Innovate.
韩梭罗让天行者卢克
Did Han Solo let Luke Skywalker
冻死在冰雪星球霍斯上了吗
freeze to death on the ice planet of Hoth?
没有
No.
他切开一只圣兽
He cut open a tauntaun
用它内部的体热给他取暖
and used its internal body heat to warm him up.
各位听见啦
You heard the man.
把他摁倒  我来剁开他
Hold him down and I'll cut him open.
等一下  我知道我不具备领导潜质
Hang on, I know I don't possess the tools of leadership,
但我不理解为什么不能在考察站
but I don't understand why we can't assemble the equipment
装配好器材然后再拿出去呢
inside the hut and then take it outside.
我没想到哦
I hadn't thought of that.
训练完毕
I guess we're done here.
来  尝尝这个
Here, drink slash eat this.
什么啊
What is it?
热巧克力加一块黄油
Hot chocolate with a stick of butter.
为啥
Okay, why?
因为在北极的严寒下
Because in the frigid temperatures in the Arctic,
我们每天至少要摄入5千卡路里
we need to consume at least 5,000 calories a day
来维持自身体重
just to maintain our body weight.
谢尔顿  你明知我不能吃黄油
Sheldon, you know I can't eat butter.
我会乳糖过敏
I'm lactose intolerant.
早就想到了  那是一块
Way ahead of you, that's an
"难以置信  居然不含黄油"[人造奶油]
"I Can't Believe It's Not Butter" stick.
妈咪  但是别人都要去北极
But mammy, all the other guys are going to the North Pole.
我不管别人做什么
I don't care what the other guys are doing.
如果他们想要跳孟加拉湾 游泳去斯里兰卡
If the other guys jumped in the Bay of Bengal and tried to swim to Sri Lanka,
你也跟着去吗
would you follow them?
你在我身后唠叨的话  我就跳
If you were standing behind me nagging, I might.
别跟你母亲顶嘴
Don't talk back to your mother.
这个太危险了  拉杰
This trip is much too dangerous, Rajesh.
不是的
No, it's not.
霍华德  告诉他们
Howard, tell them.
库萨帕里医生和夫人  你们好
Doctor and Mrs. Koothrappali, namaste.
我能理解你们的担心
I understand your concern,
如果能让你们感觉好一点 连我母亲都同意让我去呢
but if it'll make you feel any better, my mother is fine with me going,
她可是直到我17岁 才把我床上的安全栏拿掉
and this is a woman who kept a safety rail on my bed until I was 17.
她不关心她儿子 会不会被海象吃掉?
So, she has no problem with her son being eaten by a walrus?
这不可能  库萨帕里夫人
That's very unlikely, Mrs. Koothrappali.
如果拉杰死了
If Raj dies,
也只会因为冻伤  坏疽  严重晒伤
it'll be from frostbite, gangrene, acute sunburn
或者被1500磅重的北极熊撕成碎片
or being ripped to shreds by a 1,500 pound polar bear.
妈妈  我把你接到免提上 跟拉杰的父母通话
Ma, I'm putting you on speakerphone with Raj's parents.
您能告诉他们 您同意我去北极吗
Can you tell them that you're okay with me going to the Arctic?
北极
Arctic?!
我以为你说的是阿肯色州
I thought you said Arkansas!
我没那么说
I didn't say that.
你从来都不仔细听
You never listen to me!
他什么都不告诉我
He doesn't tell me anything!
他就知道自惭形秽  苟且偷生
He lives a secret life because he's ashamed!
莱纳德  能跟你谈谈吗
Hey, Leonard, can I talk to you for a sec?
当然  去外面说吧 那里少一些尖叫和罪恶
Sure, but let's go out here where there's a little less yelling and guilt.
怎么了
What's up?
我给你准备了一份送别礼物
Well, I got you a little going away present.
毯子啊
Oh, a blanket.
不对  不只是毯子
Oh, no, no, no, not just a blanket.
看见没  还有袖子呢
See, it has sleeves.
这样你就能蜷在里面
So, you can, you know, be all snoodled up
搞你的科研了
while you do your science stuff.
酷啊
Oh, wow, cool.
我会想你的
Oh, I'm gonna miss you.
-回见  -再见
- See you later. - Bye.
跟你说了  没有
I told you no!
为什么不信我
Why don't you believe me?
因为我无法理解
'Cause it doesn't make sense to me!
印度这么大一个国家
How can it be that in the entire country of India,
怎么会连一家澳美客牛排坊都没有
there isn't one Outback Steakhouse?!
谢尔顿  谢尔顿
Sheldon... Sheldon?
奶奶  我要吃饼干
I want a cookie, Meemaw.
谢尔顿  是我
Sheldon, it's me.
但是奶奶刚刚做了饼干
But Meemaw just made cookies.
我不知道该不该参加这次科考
Listen, I don't know if I can go on the expedition.
什么
What?
我觉得我不能去北极
I don't think I can go to the North Pole.
莱纳德
Okay, Leonard,
我明白 你怕我会失望
I know you're concerned about disappointing me
但我希望你能得到些许安慰
but I want you to take comfort from the knowledge
我对你的期望值其实非常低
that my expectations of you are very low.
确实很安慰人
Yeah, that's very comforting.
安慰队员是领导的职务
Comforting is a part of leadership.
我虽不在意  但仍然是我的负担
It's not a part I care for, but such is my burden.
不错  只是我觉得佩妮不想让我走
Terrific, it's just that I don't think Penny wants me to go.
假设这是不去的正当理由  实际上不是
Assuming that's a valid reason not to go, which it isn't,
你怎么知道呢 是她说的么
how do you know this? Did she say it?
不完全是吧
Not exactly.
但是她说她会想我  还送这个给我
But she said she was gonna miss me and she gave me this.
什么东西
What is it?
带袖子的毛毯
It's a blanket with sleeves.
真聪明的设计
Oh, that's clever.
看看我是否正确理解了
Let me see if I understand this correctly.
她想念你  是你非常向往的 情感状态
Her missing you is an emotional state you find desirable?
-当然啦  -那行
- Yes, obviously. - All right.
但是她想念你是建立在你要离开的基础上的
Well, given that missing you is predicated on you leaving,
从逻辑上讲  你必须去
logic dictates you must leave.
话虽如此  但这一去就是三个月啊
Yes, okay, but I'm gonna be gone for three months.
要是她不再想我了  另觅新欢怎么办
What if she doesn't miss me that long and she meets someone else?
她的注意广度[注意力集中时长]确实比较短
She does have a short attention span.
所以说  我不能去
So, I can't go.
莱纳德  也许你是对的
Leonard, you may be right.
看来佩妮暗中表现出
It appears that Penny secretly wants you
想跟你发生亲密肉体接触的欲望
in her life in a very intimate and carnal fashion.
你真的这样想?
You really think so?
当然不是
Of course not.
即使处于失眠状态  我都可以
Even in my sleep-deprived state, I've managed to
成功上演另一出经典恶作剧
pull off another one of my classic pranks.
气死你
Bazinga!
莱纳德  几点了
Oh, Leonard, what time is it?
早晨七点  抱歉这么早打扰你
It's 7:00 a.m. I'm sorry it's early,
但我们马上就出发了  我想跟你谈谈
but we're leaving soon, and I needed to talk to you.
好
Okay.
你说你会想我  是什么意思
What did you mean when you said you're going to miss me?
不知道
Um, I don't know.
你离开了  我会发现嘛
You'll be gone and I'll notice.
那这个呢
Okay, well, um, what about this?
什么意思
What does this mean?
酗酒  乱刷卡和熬夜看电视 都没啥好处
Wine, credit card and late night television are a bad combination.
好吧
All right, fine.
那个长长的拥抱呢
What about that really long hug?
那又是什么意思
What did that mean?
不算长长的拥抱呀
That wasn't a long hug.
至少持续了五秒钟
It was at least five Mississippis.
一般拥抱不超过两秒钟
A standard hug is two Mississippis tops.
莱纳德  我不知道有什么可说的
Leonard, I don't know what to tell you.
就是个拥抱嘛
It was just a hug.
很高兴交待清楚了
Glad we cleared that up.
是啊
Yeah.
后会有期
I guess I'll see you.
一路顺风
Okay, have a safe trip.
谢谢
Thank you.
-再见  -再见
- Bye. - Okay, bye.
意思是舍不得你走
It means I wish you weren't going.
该死
Damn it.
怎么了
What?
冰用完了
We're out of ice.
好了  先生们  明早七点整
All right, men, we begin initial assembly
我们开始前期装配
and deployment of the testing equipment
和部署测试仪器
starting tomorrow at 0700 hours,
在那之前的时间  你们自由支配
but until then, you are all off duty.
我建议你们 尽量别捣乱
I suggest you keep the shenanigans to a minimum
因为雪橇救护队要18小时才能到达
as medical help is 18 hours away by dogsled.
你在搞什么玩意
What are you working on?
弩弓
Crossbow.
伙计们  我能说几句吗
Hey, guys, can I just say something?
我们是不是应该仔细想想
How about we take a moment to think about
我们所在的位置
where we are right now?
这算是 世界之巅了
This is literally the top of the world.
人类历史上只有屈指可数的几位
Only a handful of people in all of human history
能目睹我们看到的景象
will ever see what we are going to see.
他说得对
He's right.
是啊
Yeah, wow.
相当有纪念意义
It is remarkable.
谁想看电影
So, who's up for a movie?
好主意  看什么呢
Good idea, what do you think?
《大北极》还是约翰·卡朋特的《怪形》
Ice Station Zebra or John Carpenter's The Thing?
双片连映吧
I say double feature.
晚餐好了
Dinner's ready!
吃什么
What are we having?
"再造"泰国菜
Reconstituted Thai food.
-带了脱水低钠酱油吗  -带了
- Did you bring the dehydrated low-sodium soy sauce? - Check.
-冻干辣芥末  -带了
- Freeze-dried spicy mustard? - Check.
速冻糙米  不是白米
Flash-frozen brown rice, not white?
抱歉
Uh, oh, sorry.
别担心
Not to worry.
我藏起来了
I hid it.
气死你
Bazinga!
你占了我的专座
You're in my spot.
等不及做弩弓了 给我找根冰柱
There's no time for a crossbow. Find me an icicle.
三个月啊  真是爽到家了
Three months. This is gonna be great!
本季大爆炸完结
感谢大家一直以来对大爆炸的支持及厚爱
下一季度  请继续锁定 YYets